[
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"_____ in the name of love?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stop"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"\"He's So Fine\", \"One Fine Day\" and \"A Love So Fine\" where hits for what fine group?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["The Chiffons"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"\"Joy to the World\" was a hit in 1971 for what band with three lead vocalists?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Three Dog Night"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"A __________ helps to set and maintain your tempo while playing.", "answer":0, "answers":["Metronome"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"A graphical representation of the guitar fingerboard, used to teach someone to play a guitar without actually learning how to read musical notes.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tablature"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"A set of graduated steel bars set in a frame and hit with a hammer, used in the orchestra.", "answer":0, "answers":["Glockenspiel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"About which family are the Godfather films?", "answer":0, "answers":["Corleone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Actor: _______ Borgnine.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ernest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Actor: ________ Hackman.", "answer":0, "answers":["Gene"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Actor: __________ Nimoy.", "answer":0, "answers":["Leonard"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Actor: __________ Savalas.", "answer":0, "answers":["Telly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"After who was Deana Carter named?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dean Martin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Alvin & Simon had a brother called ____.", "answer":0, "answers":["Theodore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"An adventurous penguin named Tennessee Tuxedo had a sidekick named _______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chumley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"An adventurous penguin named Tennessee Tuxedo had a sidekick named _______", "answer":0, "answers":["Chumley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"An alien creature in a funny hat has opposed both Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck.  Where is he from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mars"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"An alien creature in a funny hat has opposed both Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck. Where is he from", "answer":0, "answers":["Mars"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"An Andy Panda cartoon gave birth to a famous, cantankerous bird. Name him.", "answer":0, "answers":["Woody woodpecker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"An arrangement for five performers is called a:", "answer":0, "answers":["Quintet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Andre Rieu and the Johann Strauss Orchestra are famous for what musical love piece", "answer":0, "answers":["Romeo and Juliet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"As what is Merle Haggard also known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Okie from Muskogee"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"As who is Terry Bollea known?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hulk Hogan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"At the end of \"Planet of the Apes\" what protruded from the rocks?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Statue of Liberty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Band: \" _________ And the Bad Seeds\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Nick Cave"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Band: Elvis Costello and the ___________ ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Attractions"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Barbara Streisand was the female lead in \"Hello, Dolly\".  Who was the male lead?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Walter Matthau"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Beethoven's Sixth Symphony shares it's popular name with a method of animal farming. What is it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pastoral"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Before being married to Pamela Anderson what other famous actress was Tommy Lee married to?", "answer":0, "answers":["Heather Locklear"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Before Olive Oil met Popeye she was engaged to someone.  Who was he?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ham Gravy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Before Olive Oil met Popeye she was engaged to someone. Who was he", "answer":0, "answers":["Ham gravyzzcomment: olive oyl was wrong, jono82 said"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Benny and Cecil were at odds with whom?", "answer":0, "answers":["John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Benny and Cecil were at odds with whom", "answer":0, "answers":["John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Besides \"Auld Lang Syne\" and \"For He's a Jolly Good Fellow\", what is the most frequently sung song in English?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Happy Birthday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Besides the Stones, which group had the longest touring career until the founder's death in 1995?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Grateful Dead"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Bill Justis was a studio musician when he recorded this 'sloppy' instrumental in october 1957?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raunchy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Broke Batman", "answer":0, "answers":["Bane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Bugs always finds himself at the wrong end of a gun, usually toted by either Elmer Fudd or who?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yosemite Sam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Bugs always finds himself at the wrong end of a gun, usually toted by either Elmer Fudd or who", "answer":0, "answers":["Yosemite sam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Casper the Friendly Ghost frolicked with which witch?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wendy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Casper the Friendly Ghost frolicked with which witch", "answer":0, "answers":["Wendy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Charles Boyer inspired a cartoon skunk. Who?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pepe le Pew"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Charles Boyer inspired a cartoon skunk. Who", "answer":0, "answers":["Pepe le pew"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Charles Laughton played Quasimodo in this epic film.", "answer":0, "answers":["Hunchback of Notre Dame"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Composer of the Brandenburg Concerti: J.S. ____", "answer":0, "answers":["Bach"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Country singer Vince ____?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Crosby, Stills and Nash's debut album included a song about a girl and the colour of her eyes. Name that song.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sweet Judy Blue Eyes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Current leader of Justice League America", "answer":0, "answers":["Wonder woman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Darth Vader was the villan in the movie, \"____ Wars\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Star"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Donald Duck comics were banned in Finland because he didn't wear ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pants"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Famous Phrases: Who knows The ______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Shadow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Famous Phrases: Who knows? The ______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Shadow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Fat Albert and friends was created by ______ ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill Cosby"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Fifties rock \"n\" roll was revived by what greased hair, T-shirted, TV frequenting group?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Sha Na Na"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Film Title: ______ (a number) Leagues Under the Sea.", "answer":0, "answers":["20000"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Film Title: An Officer and a(n) _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Gentleman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Film Title: Fahrenheit ________. (a number)", "answer":0, "answers":["451"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Film Title: The Last Days of _________. (a city)", "answer":0, "answers":["Pompeii"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"For which ad campaign was the line 'I can't believe I ate the whole thing' used?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alka Seltzer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"For which cartoon character was Beethoven a favourite composer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shroeder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"For which film did Art Carney win best actor Oscar in 1974?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harry and Tonto"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"For whom did Colonel Tom Parker act as manager?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Presley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Formerly with Spencer Davis, he went on to form Traffic with Dave Mason. He is?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Winwood"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Forrest ____ liked shrimp.", "answer":0, "answers":["Gump"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"French impressionist Claude _______", "answer":0, "answers":["Debussy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"From what platform does the 'Chattanooga Choo Choo' leave Pennsylvania station?", "answer":0, "answers":["29"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"From where was Ricky in 'I Love Lucy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cuba"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"From which station does the 'Chattanooga Choo Choo' leave?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pennsylvania station"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Gadzookie has a large, green friend. Who is he?", "answer":0, "answers":["Godzilla"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Gadzookie has a large, green friend. Who is he", "answer":0, "answers":["Godzilla"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Girlfriend of Lex Luther II", "answer":0, "answers":["Supergirl"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Green Lantern's alter ego", "answer":0, "answers":["Hal jordan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Group of heroes led by Dick Grayson", "answer":0, "answers":["New titans"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Hang On Sloopy' was the official rock song of which band?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ohio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Hanna_Barbera rose to fame by creating what duo for MGM", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom and jerry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Hanna-Barbera rose to fame by creating what duo for MGM?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom and Jerry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He directed \"The Godfather\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Francis Ford Coppola"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He directed the movie E.T.", "answer":0, "answers":["Stephen Spielberg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He played Superman in the 1978 movie version.", "answer":0, "answers":["Christopher Reeve"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He starred in, \"City Lights\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlie Chaplin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He was known as the \"Elephant Man\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Joseph Merrick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He was the villain in \"Star Wars\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Darth Vader"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He was the voice of draco the dragon in the movie Dragonheart.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sean Connery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"He wrote the operas \"The Magic Flute\" and \"The Marriage of Figaro\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Hey! What was the name of the hit song released by 'The Romantics' in February 1980?", "answer":0, "answers":["That's What I Like About You"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"His films include: Giant, Written on the Wind, and A Farewell to Arms.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rock Hudson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"His films include: Spartacus, The Vikings, and Ulysses.", "answer":0, "answers":["Kirk Douglas"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mental powers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane", "answer":0, "answers":["Mental powers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many flats are in the key of B flat major?", "answer":0, "answers":["Two"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many freckles did Howdy Doody have?", "answer":0, "answers":["Forty eight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many members are in the 'fairfield four'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many Oscars did Ben Hur win?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many semitones are there in an octave?", "answer":0, "answers":["12"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many storm troopers were seen in Star Trek?", "answer":0, "answers":["None (It Was Star Wars)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many strings are there on a bass guitar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many strings are there on a standard guitar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Six"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many strings are there on a violin?", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many strings does a harp have?", "answer":0, "answers":["47"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How many symphonies did Beethoven complete?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How old was Leann Rhimes when she became a country music star?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fourteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"How old was Leann Rhimes when she recorded her first album?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Ian Gillain is the singer for this legendary band", "answer":0, "answers":["Deep Purple"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 'Coronation Street', who is Ken and Denise's son?", "answer":0, "answers":["Daniel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 'La Traviata', what does Violetta sing?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sempre Libera"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 'La Traviata', who sings 'Sempre Libera'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Violetta"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 'Star Wars', who was C3P0's sidekick?", "answer":0, "answers":["R2D2"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 'The Shining' what was the child's imaginary friend's name (the one who told him things that were going to happen)?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tony"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In \"Gone With the Wind\", Scarlett regains her wealth by investing in what type of business?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Sawmill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 1958, who had a pop music hit with 'Willie and the Hand Jive'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Johnny Otis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 1962 Chubby Checker had a hit with a pop song and novelty dance that remains famous today. What was that dance?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Twist"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 1968, who released 'Carnival of life' and 'Recital'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lee Michaels"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 1975 Jack Nicholson won the best actor Oscar for his role in this film.", "answer":0, "answers":["One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 1981, who won song of the year with 'Sailing'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christopher Cross"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In 1987, who released her second album 'Solitude Standing'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Suzanne Vega"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In a 1976 release, who wanted to 'fly like an eagle'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Miller Band"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In late 1957, Buddy Holly's solo release 'Peggy Sue' challenged which song recorded with The Crickets?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oh Boy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the 'Nightmare On Elm Street' films, who played Freddy Krueger?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Englund"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the 1996 version of \"Romeo and Juliet\", who played Juliet?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Claire Danes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the 60s Mokees Song Here comes Tommorow who does Davey Jones say he Loves?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sandra and Mary"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the 70s Hit Captain Scarlet and the Mysterons what is the name of the company Scralet works for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spectrum"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the cartoons who was Hokie Wolf's sidekick?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ding"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the cartoons who was Hokie Wolf's sidekick", "answer":0, "answers":["Ding"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the children's tv series 'Sesame Street', what two characters were roomates?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bert and Ernie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film 'American Hot Wax', who did Jay Leno play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mookie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film 'American Hot Wax', who played the 'Mookie'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jay Leno"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film 'Hackers', how old was 'zero_kool' when he was first arrested?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eleven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film 'Home Alone', who played the baddies?", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Pesci and Daniel Stern"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film 'Pretty Woman', for who was Goldie Hawn the body double?", "answer":0, "answers":["Julia Roberts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film 'The Day Of The Jackal', who played the Jackal?", "answer":0, "answers":["Edward Fox"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the film \"Bright Eyes\", Shirley Temple sang about this boat.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["The Good Ship Lollipop"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the Gene Pitney how many hours was it from Tulsa?", "answer":0, "answers":["24"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the opera 'Don Giovanni', what was Leporello?", "answer":0, "answers":["Servant"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the TV series 'Seinfeld', who does Michael Richards play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kramer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the TV series 'Seinfeld', who plays Kramer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Richards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the TV series 'The Brady Bunch', what was Cindy's toy doll's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kitty Carrie All"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the TV series 'The Fall Guy', who did Lee Majors play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Colt Seavers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the TV series 'The Fall Guy', who played Colt Seavers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lee Majors"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In the TV sitcom 'Married With Children', what is the dog's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Buck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In this 1968 film the husband of an unsuspecting young wife becomes involved with a witch's coven.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rosemary's Baby"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In what city does Fat Albert live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philadelphia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In what city does Fat Albert live", "answer":0, "answers":["Philadelphia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In what did someone squish her hands to make the sound of e.t walking?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jelly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In what film did Whoopi Goldberg make her screen debut?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Color Purple"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In what year did both Peanuts and Beetle Bailey first appear", "answer":0, "answers":["1950"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which Disney movie is the song \"So This Is Love\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cinderella"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which film did Henry Fonda play a fallen priest?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Fugitive"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which film did Jay Leno play 'Mookie'?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Hot Wax"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which film did Paul Newman and Robert Redford hold hands and jump into a river?", "answer":0, "answers":["Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which film was Goldie Hawn the body double for Julia Roberts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pretty Woman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which James Bond film does the villain cheat at golf?", "answer":0, "answers":["Goldfinger"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which London recording studios did The Beatles record the majority of their work?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abbey Road"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which movie did Bruce Willis play the role of Corben Dallas?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Fifth Element"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which opera does Leporello entertain a vengeful jilted lover?", "answer":0, "answers":["Don Giovanni"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"In which Verdi opera does Violetta sing 'Sempre Libera'?", "answer":0, "answers":["La Traviata"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Jerry Lee Lewis had Great _____ Of Fire.", "answer":0, "answers":["Balls!"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"John Travolta, Samuel Jackson, Uma Thurman starred in which 1994 Quentin Tarantino film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pulp Fiction"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Josie and the ________", "answer":0, "answers":["Pussycats"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Juliette Binoche won an academy award for best supporting role in which film?", "answer":0, "answers":["English Patient"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Kelsey Grammer sings and plays the theme song for which TV show?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frasier"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Killed Superman", "answer":0, "answers":["Doomsday"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Mel Blanc, the voice of Bugs Bunny, was allergic to what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carrots"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Mentor of Titan had two children in the Marvel comics, Thanos and ____", "answer":0, "answers":["Ero"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Mentor of Titan had two children in the Marvel comics, Thanos and ___?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ero"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Michael di Lorenzo was one of the lead dancers on which Michael Jackson video?", "answer":0, "answers":["Beat It"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Mickey Mouse is known as what in Italy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Topolino"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Miss Buckley is secretary to what commanding officer?", "answer":0, "answers":["General Halftrack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Miss Buckley is secretary to what commanding officer", "answer":0, "answers":["General halftrack"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Alley Oop's girl friend.", "answer":0, "answers":["Oola"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Alley Oop's girl friend", "answer":0, "answers":["Oola"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Alvin & Simon's brother was ________", "answer":0, "answers":["Theo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Cathy's on again/off again boy friend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Irving"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Cathy's on again/off again boy friend", "answer":0, "answers":["Irving"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Dennis the Menace's next door neighbors.", "answer":0, "answers":["Mr and Mrs Wilson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Donald Duck's girlfriend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Daisy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Donald Duck's girlfriend", "answer":0, "answers":["Daisy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Hagar the Horrible's dog.", "answer":0, "answers":["Snert"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Jerry Garcia's long lived group.", "answer":0, "answers":["The Grateful Dead"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name Li'l Abner's favorite Indian drink.", "answer":0, "answers":["Kickapoo joy juice"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the actor who played the leading role in \"The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Clint Eastwood"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the apartments the Jetson's live in.", "answer":0, "answers":["The skypad apartments"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Add It Up, Blister In The Sun, Kiss Off\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Violet Femmes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Aqualung, Thick as a Brick\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jethro Tull"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Baby I Don't Care, I Want Your Love\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Transvision Vamp"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Black Night, Smoke On The Water\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Deep Purple"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Doctor Doctor, Hold Me Now, Don't Mess With Dr Dream\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thompson Twins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Forgiven Not Forgotten, Runaway\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Coors"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Get Down & Get With It, Mama We're All Crazy Now\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slade"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Heart of Glass, The Tide is High\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blondie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Let's Stick Together, The Price of Love\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bryan Ferry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Light My Fire, Love Her Madly\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Doors"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Mystify, Listen Like Thieves, Original Sin\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["INXS"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Psycho Killer, Road To Nowhere\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Talkingheads"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Sex & Drugs & Rock & Roll, I Want To Be Straight\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Drury and The Blockheads"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the band - songs include \"Strange Brew, White Room\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cream"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the Disney cartoon in which the character \"Belle\" appears.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Beauty and the Beast"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the dog in the Yankee Doodle cartoons.", "answer":0, "answers":["Chopper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the European hit, now an animated series about underwater people.", "answer":0, "answers":["The Snorks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the fastest mouse in all of Mexico.", "answer":0, "answers":["Speedy Gonzalez"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the fastest mouse in all of Mexico", "answer":0, "answers":["Speedy gonzalez"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the late actor who played Obi-Wan Kenobi in Star Wars?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alec Guiness"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the musical film named after a state.", "answer":0, "answers":["Oklahoma"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the ranger who was always after Yogi Bear.", "answer":0, "answers":["Rick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the singer - songs include \"Me & Bobby McGee, Mercedes Benz\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Janis Joplin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Name the town that Fred, Wilma, Barney, and Betty lived in.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bedrock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Nick Nolte and Eddie Murphy star in this 1982 film.", "answer":0, "answers":["48 Hours"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Number of new Supermen after his \"death\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Four"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Of the new Supermen, this one was a villain", "answer":0, "answers":["Cyborg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"On 'Dragnet', who played officer Bill Gannon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harry Morgan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"On 'The Lucy Show', who played Vivian Bagley?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vivian Vance"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"On what LP Cover can we read the words 'Welcome Rolling Stones'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sergeant Pepper´s Lonely Hearts Club Band"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"On what T.V. show could Tom Terrific be found?", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain Kangaroo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"On what T.V. show could Tom Terrific be found", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain kangaroo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Orson Wells was nominated for four oscars for which legendary movie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Citizen Kane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Pancho was whose faithful sidekick?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cisco Kid's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Paul Mccartney played these instruments?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bass guitar and piano"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Peter Sellers is best known for his role as Inspector _________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Clouseau"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Photographer for Daily Planet", "answer":0, "answers":["Jimmy olsen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Popeye's chief adversary has two names, Bluto and ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brutus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Popeye's chief adversary has two names, Bluto and ______", "answer":0, "answers":["Brutus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Porky Pig had a girlfriend named ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Petunia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Porky Pig had a girlfriend named _______.", "answer":0, "answers":["Pet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"R. Kelly sings: 'If I can see it then I can do it, if I just believe it, there's nothing to it'. What's the song title?", "answer":0, "answers":["I Believe I Can Fly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Randy Travis said his love was 'deeper than the ______'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Holler"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Richard Strauss' majestic overture \"Also Sprach Zarathustra\" was the theme music for which Stanley Kubrick film?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["2001 : A Space Odyessy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Rolling Stones first hit was written by what group?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Beatles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Russian modernist Igor _________", "answer":0, "answers":["Stravinsky"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Savage Garden took 13 nominations and 10 wins at which awards?", "answer":0, "answers":["ARIA awards"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Arthur Curry", "answer":0, "answers":["Aquaman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Boston Brand", "answer":0, "answers":["Deadman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Bruce Wayne", "answer":0, "answers":["Batman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Clark Kent", "answer":0, "answers":["Superman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Cliff Steele", "answer":0, "answers":["Robotman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Jay Garrick", "answer":0, "answers":["The flash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Jim Corrigan", "answer":0, "answers":["The spectre"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Jimmy Olson", "answer":0, "answers":["Elastic lad"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Jonn Jonzz", "answer":0, "answers":["Martian manhunter"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Kay Challis", "answer":0, "answers":["Crazy jane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Kirk Morrison", "answer":0, "answers":["King mob"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Lyta Trevor", "answer":0, "answers":["Fury"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Maggie Sawyer", "answer":0, "answers":["Maggie sawyer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Secret Identities: Wally West", "answer":0, "answers":["The flash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"She played a Polish refugee in \"Sophie's Choice\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Meryl Streep"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"She played Lois Lane in the 1978 film version of \"Superman\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Margot Kidder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"She played the lead role in \"Coal Miner's Daughter\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Sissy Spacek"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"She starred in the 1952 film, \"Niagara\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Singer Paula ______?", "answer":0, "answers":["Abdul"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Singing without instrumental back up is called what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Capella"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Sung by Robert Palmer, '______ to love'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Addicted"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Tarzan had a chimpanzee, what was his name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cheetah"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Tess Trueheart married which plainclothes detective?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dick Tracy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Tess Trueheart married which plainclothes detective", "answer":0, "answers":["Dick tracy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The director of Jaws, Raiders of the Lost Ark", "answer":0, "answers":["Stephen spielberg"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The eldest sister in the TV Series Charmed, is played by who?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shannon Doherty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The film 'The Wizard Of ______'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The film \"Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon\" takes place in which dynasty (- the ' )\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Ching"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The first 18 minutes of this movie is black and white.", "answer":0, "answers":["Wizard of Oz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The Hard Rock Cafe is named after a song by what band?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Doors"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The initials of the band NIN stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine Inch Nails"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The key of A major has ___ sharps.", "answer":0, "answers":["Three"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The maiden names of which two cartoon characters are Slaghoople and Mcbricker?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wilma Flintstone and Betty Rubble"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The rolling stones first recorded song was?", "answer":0, "answers":["Come On"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The song \"Matchmaker, Matchmaker\" came from which musical play?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Fiddler On The Roof"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The standard major scale is also known as the _______ mode.", "answer":0, "answers":["Ionian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The theme tune for 'Monty Python's Flying Circus' was written by which composer?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Philip Sousa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The two rival gangs in \"West Side Story\" were the Sharks and the _________.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Jets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The Who' had a guiness world record for what?", "answer":0, "answers":["Loudest Band"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"The Who's rock musical stars Elton John.  It's called ________.", "answer":0, "answers":["Tommy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This 1974 film started a run of nostalgia culminating in the TV series \"Happy Days\".", "answer":0, "answers":["American Graffiti"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This actress appeared in \"St. Elmo's Fire\", \"The Scarlett Letter\", and \"Striptease\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Demi Moore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This band's highly original video for \"Whip it,\" characterized by red flower pot hats was criticized for being both sado-masochistic and racist?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Devo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This band's highly original video for \"Whip it,\" characterized by red flower pot hats was criticized for being both sado-masochistic and racist.\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Devo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This Disney movie relies heavily on computer animation.", "answer":0, "answers":["TRON"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This electronic instrument's creator was surnamed Moog, and his models are worth a fortune! Other brands include Roland, Korg, and Casio.", "answer":0, "answers":["Synthesizer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This female artist enjoyed sucess on both popular and country & western stations with such tunes as \"Let Me Be There\" and \"Have You Never Been Mellow.\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Olivia Newton-John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This film starring Julie Andrews and Christopher Plummer wont he best picture Oscar for 1965.", "answer":0, "answers":["Sound of Music"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This film starring Richard Beymer and Natalie Wood won the best picture Oscar for 1961.", "answer":0, "answers":["West Side Story"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This film was an ambitious concert sequence of cartoons by Walt Disney.", "answer":0, "answers":["Fantasia"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This gypsy swing guitarist nearly had his left hand destroyed by fire as a child?", "answer":0, "answers":["Django Reinhardt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This is a classic film about a huge gorilla.", "answer":0, "answers":["King Kong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This magic word was in the movie, \"Mary Poppins\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This movie directed by Woody Allen won the best picture Oscar in 1978.", "answer":0, "answers":["Annie Hall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This movie is about the migration of poor workers from the dust bowl to the Californian fruit valleys.", "answer":0, "answers":["The Grapes of Wrath"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This movie starring Marlon Brando won the best picture award in 1972.", "answer":0, "answers":["The Godfather"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This term means to play crisply, with the notes separated?", "answer":0, "answers":["Staccato"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This term means to play moderately slow and gracefully?", "answer":0, "answers":["Adagio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This term means to play smoothly?", "answer":0, "answers":["Legato"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This term means to play smoothly.", "answer":0, "answers":["Legato"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This was the Beatle's first film.", "answer":0, "answers":["A Hard Day's Night"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This was the first 3-D film.", "answer":0, "answers":["Bwana Devil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This was the first cartoon talking picture.", "answer":0, "answers":["Steamboat Willie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This was the sequel to \"Star Wars\".", "answer":0, "answers":["The Empire Strikes Back"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"This was the sequel to \"The Empire Strikes Back\".", "answer":0, "answers":["Return of the Jedi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Through 1963 this duo's total record sales exceeded 18 million with successes including \"Cathy's Clown\" and \"Wake Up Little Suzie\".", "answer":0, "answers":["The Everly Brothers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Tinky winky, Dipsy LaLa and Po are know as what?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Teletubbies"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Tippi Hedren is best known for her lead role in which film?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Birds"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"To gradually decrease in volume?", "answer":0, "answers":["Decrescendo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"To gradually decrease in volume.", "answer":0, "answers":["Decrescendo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"To play music smoothly?", "answer":0, "answers":["Legato"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"To which elemetary school did TV's 'Brady Bunch' go?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dixie Canyon Elementary"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Turn, Side and Why does it always rain on me are all songs from what UK band?", "answer":0, "answers":["Travis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"TV series: 'American ______'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bandstand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Vincent Vega appeared in which movie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pulp Fiction"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Was Shirley Temple 21, 25 or 29 when she made her last film?", "answer":0, "answers":["21"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What actor appeared in all three of these films, Straw Dogs, Midnight Cowboy, and The Graduate?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dustin Hoffman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What actress has received the most Oscar nominations?", "answer":0, "answers":["Katherine Hepburn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What actress's real name was Frances Gumm?", "answer":0, "answers":["Judy Garland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What album holds the world record for copies sold?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thriller"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What are the names of Donald Duck's nephews?", "answer":0, "answers":["Huey Dewey and Louey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What are the separators on a guitar neck called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What band recorded the 1978 hit album: \"Briefcase Full of Blues\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Blues Brothers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What came out of Milton's head?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What came out of Milton's head", "answer":0, "answers":["Steam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What character did Tex Avery first create upon arriving at MGM?", "answer":0, "answers":["Screwball Squirrel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What character did Tex Avery first create upon arriving at MGM", "answer":0, "answers":["Screwball squirrel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What city do Batman and Robin patrol?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gotham City"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What city is also known as Music City, U.S.A.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nashville"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What city's police force did Charlie Chan work with?", "answer":0, "answers":["Honolulu"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What classic rock band sang the song 'Paint It, Black'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rolling Stones"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What color was Bullitt's car?", "answer":0, "answers":["Green"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What colour is Art & Literature in the standard edition of \"Trivial Pursuit\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brown"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What comic strip character is Beetle Bailey's sister?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lois (of Hi and Lois)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What comic strip character is Beetle Bailey's sister", "answer":0, "answers":["Lois (of hi and lois )"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What composer was working on his 10th symphony at the time of his death?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ludwig van Beethoven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What country singer/songwriter (and sometimes actor) is known as \"the country outlaw\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Willie Nelson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What country was the setting for \"The King and I\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Siam (Thailand)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What detective duo was featured in Mystery at Devil's Paw?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hardy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Dagwood give up to marry Blondie?", "answer":0, "answers":["A family inheritance"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Dagwood give up to marry Blondie", "answer":0, "answers":["A family inheritance"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Dorothy's house land on in 'The Wizard Of Oz'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Wicked Witch of the West"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Dr. David Banner become when he got angry?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Incredible Hulk"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did George Harrison discover on the Witwatersrand?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gold"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Hannibal Lecter like to eat with liver?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fava Beans"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Peppermint Patty always call Charlie Brown?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chuck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Peppermint Patty always call Charlie Brown", "answer":0, "answers":["Chuck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did Sheryl Crow do before she became a singer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Teach"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What did TVs IMF stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Impossible Mission Forces"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What do the initials B.B. stand for in B.B. King's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blues Boy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What do the initials of the band NIN stand for?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nine Inch Nails"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What does Steven Spielberg try to include in every film he makes, claiming it is for luck?", "answer":0, "answers":["Scene With A Shooting Star"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What does the Italian term \"poco a poco\" mean?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Little by little"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What does the statue of Oscar stand on?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Reel of Film"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What does the term 'DJ' mean?", "answer":0, "answers":["Disc Jockey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What Don Mclean song laments the day Buddy Holly died?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Pie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What entertainer is allowing one of his songs to be used in a government campaign to beat drunk driving?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Jackson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What expression did Clark Kent's newspaper boss like to use?", "answer":0, "answers":["Great Caesar's ghost!"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What famous animal character called \"Skull Island\" home?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["King Kong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What famous classical composer continued to compose great music after becoming deaf?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ludwig van Beethoven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What famous singer was known to give automobiles to complete strangers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Presley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film did John Wayne win his only Oscar for?", "answer":0, "answers":["True Grit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film featured a cat named Mr. Bigglesworth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Austin Powers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film is generally considered the worst film ever made?", "answer":0, "answers":["Attack of the Killer Tomatoes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film marked James Cagney's return to the screen after 20 years?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ragtime"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film starred Helen Hunt, Cary Elwes and Bill Paxton?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twister"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film starred Rosie O'Donnell, Rita Wilson and Meg Ryan?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sleepless in Seattle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What film was the last featuring Mel Blanc's voice?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jetsons"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What group refused to have their pictures taken while they were not in their makeup?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kiss"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What group's biggest-ever hit was Be My Baby?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Ronettes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What hardcore rock group sings, 'Blind' and 'Clown'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Korn"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What instrument are you playing when you perform a rim shot?", "answer":0, "answers":["Drums"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What instrument does an organ grinder play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hurdy gurdy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What instrument does Woody Allen play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Clarinet"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is a cello's full name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Violoncello"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is a Hurdy-Gurdy?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Fiddle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is a violoncello usually called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cello"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Batman's butler Alfred's last name.", "answer":0, "answers":["Pennyworth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Blondie's maiden name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oop"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Blondie's maiden name", "answer":0, "answers":["Oop"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Cape Town's major choir called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Philharmonic choir"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Cher's maiden name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sarkassian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Dennis the Menace's last name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mitchell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Dennis the Menace's last name", "answer":0, "answers":["Mitchell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Dennis the Menace's surname?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mitchell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Elton John's real name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Reginald Dwight"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Hawkeye's full name in M.A.S.H.?", "answer":0, "answers":["Benjamin Franklin Pierce"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Hulk Hogan's real name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Terry Bollea"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Kenny G's real surname?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gorelick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Kermit D Frog's girlfriend's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Miss Piggy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is know as 'The Greatest Show On Earth'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Barnum & Bailey Circus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Peter Parker's secret identity?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spiderman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Smokey Stover's job", "answer":0, "answers":["Fireman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Super Chicken's partners name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Super Chicken's partners name", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is tattooed on Glen Campbell's arm?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dagger"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the address of The Munsters?", "answer":0, "answers":["1313 Mockingbird Lane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the destination of the plane at the end of the film \"Casablanca\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lisbon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the drummer's name in 'The Muppet Show'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Animal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the frog's name in 'The Muppet Show'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kermit D Frog"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the longest running musical in Broadway history?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cats"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the mother's name in Family Circus?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thelma"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the mother's name in Family Circus", "answer":0, "answers":["Thelma"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name given to the type of West Indian music made famous by artists such as Bob Marley and Peter Tosh?", "answer":0, "answers":["Reggae"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of Duddley Do_Right's horse", "answer":0, "answers":["Horse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of Duddley Do-Right's horse?", "answer":0, "answers":["Horse"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of Jaleel White's character in the tv series 'Family ties'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Urkel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of Pearce Brosnan's first James Bond film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Goldeneye"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the Family Circus's dog?", "answer":0, "answers":["Barf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the Family Circus's dog", "answer":0, "answers":["Barf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the film in which Steven Segal's character dies?", "answer":0, "answers":["Executive Decision"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the Indian musical instrument made popular in western rock by The Beatles and Ravi Shankar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sitar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the rabbit in the film, \"Bambi\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Thumper"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the skunk in the film, \"Bambi\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Flower"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the Volkswagen in the film, \"The Love Bug\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Herbie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of the whale that swallowed Pinocchio.", "answer":0, "answers":["Monstro"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the name of Yogi Bear's best freind", "answer":0, "answers":["Boo Boo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the official birthplace of country music?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bristol"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the only X Rated film to have won the best film Oscar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Midnight Cowboy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the Pink panter in the Pink Pather film?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Diamond"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the sequel to the film 'Every Which Way But Loose'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Every Which Way You Can"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the stage name of Greta Gustafson?", "answer":0, "answers":["Greta Garbo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the term used for 'slowly' in music?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lento"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is the title of the 1996 sequel to \"Terms of Endearment\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Morning Star"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Tina Turner's real name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Anne Mae Bullock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What is Vanilla Ice's real name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert van Winkle"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What job was Sting before he was a rock star?", "answer":0, "answers":["Teacher"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What kind of creature was Chewbacca in \"Star Wars\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wookiee"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What kind of dog is Scooby Doo?", "answer":0, "answers":["Great dane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What kind of dog is Scooby Doo", "answer":0, "answers":["Great dane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What kind of eyes did the girl in \"Lucy In The Sky With Diamonds\" have?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Kaleidoscope"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What license plate number is on the Volkswagon on the cover of The Beatles' 'Abbey Road' Album?", "answer":0, "answers":["281F"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What Magician walked through the great wall of china?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Copperfield"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What Marlon Brando film was widely banned?", "answer":0, "answers":["Last Tango In Paris"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What movie starred Nicholas Cage and John Travolta, one as a police officer, the other as a villain?", "answer":0, "answers":["Face Off"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What musical instrument did Jack Benny play?", "answer":0, "answers":["Violin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What night club did Ricky work at on 'I Love Lucy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Tropicana"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What other well known singer shares the same birthday as Elvis Presley (Jan 8)?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Bowie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What Procol Harem tune was based on the Bach cantata \"Sleepers Awake\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Whiter Shade of Pale"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What show/game has characters such as Bulbasaur and Pikachu?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pokemon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What song by Don McLean talks about the day Buddy Holly died?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Pie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What song did Aretha Franklin sing in \"The Blues Brothers\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Think"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What song did Elton John and George Michael sing as a duet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Don't Let The Sun Go Down On Me"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What song was originally 'Good Morning To You' before the words were changed and it was published in 1935?", "answer":0, "answers":["Happy Birthday To You"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What song's words were changed and then published in 1935 as 'Happy Birthday To You'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Good Morning To You"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What term is used for the speed at which a piece of music is played ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tempo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What TV network features programming just for children?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nickelodeon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What TV series from 1970-1974 starred Susan Dey?", "answer":0, "answers":["Partridge Family"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What two words are normally at the end of most movies?", "answer":0, "answers":["The End"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What type of plant does Broom Hilda sell?", "answer":0, "answers":["Venus flytrap"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What type of plant does Broom Hilda sell", "answer":0, "answers":["Venus flytrap"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was \"Rocky's\" last name?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Balboa"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Ben Stiller's character called in 'Mystery Men'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mr. Furious"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Betty Grable's nickname?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Legs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Citizen Kane's dying word?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rosebud"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Citizen Kane's first name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Daffy Duck's favorite insult?", "answer":0, "answers":["You're dispicable!"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Daffy Ducks usual closing line", "answer":0, "answers":["You're dispicable !"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Don Rickles' nickname?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mr. Warmth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Dorothy's last name in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gale"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Eddie Murphy's character name in 'Beverley Hills Cop'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Axel Foley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Elvis Presley's twin brother's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Garon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Elvis Presley's wife's name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Priscilla"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Eric Claptons Nick Name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slowhand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Garth's last name in 'Wayne's World'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Algar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was George of the Jungle always running in to?", "answer":0, "answers":["A tree"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was George of the Jungle always running in to", "answer":0, "answers":["Tree"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Jethro Tull before donating his name to a British epic rock group?", "answer":0, "answers":["Agriculturist"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was John Wayne's real name?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marion Morrison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Keanu Reeves' computer world alias in 'The Matrix'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Neo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Keanu Reeves' first big film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Point Break"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Kevin Bacon's first big hit?", "answer":0, "answers":["Footloose"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Lucy's maiden name on 'I Love Lucy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["McGillicuddy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Marilyn Monroe's given name at birth?", "answer":0, "answers":["Norma Jean Mortenson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was painted on Peter Fonda's helmet motorcycle helmet in 'Easy Rider'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stars and stripes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Rocky's nickname in the ring?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Italian Stallion"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was Sir Alec Guinness's role in \"Star Wars\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Obi-Wan Kenobi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the average age of United States soldiers in the Vietnam war?", "answer":0, "answers":["Nineteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was The Beatles' biggest hit single?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hey Jude"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first cartoon character called?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oswald the Rabbit"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first cartoon to feature sound?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steamboat Willie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first cartoon to feature sound", "answer":0, "answers":["Steamboat willy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first CD pressed in the USA?", "answer":0, "answers":["Born In The USA"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first film directed by Robert Redford?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ordinary People"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first James Bond Film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr. No"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the first network series devoted entirely to rock and roll?", "answer":0, "answers":["American Bandstand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the last Beatles album to be released before they broke up in 1970?", "answer":0, "answers":["Let It Be"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the last movie of the late Brandon Lee?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Crow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name given to the popular genre of rock that arose in the Pacific Northwest (Seattle) in the early 1990s.", "answer":0, "answers":["Grunge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Ashley Wilkes' plantation in \"Gone With the Wind\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Twelve Oaks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Barney and Betty Rubble's son?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bam Bam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of George of the Jungle's pet elephant?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shep"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of George of the Jungle's pet elephant", "answer":0, "answers":["Shep"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Han Solo's spaceship in \"Star Wars\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Millennium Falcon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Luke's strange little advisor in \"The Empire Strikes Back\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yoda"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Ross' pet monkey on 'Friends'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marcel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Speed Racer's car?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Mach Five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of Speed Racer's car", "answer":0, "answers":["The mach five"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of the motel in the film \"Psycho\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bates Motel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of the pinball machine in the film 'Tommy'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wizard"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of the restaurant the TV series \"Happy Days\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Arnolds"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the name of the two space shuttles in 'Armegeddon'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Freedom and Independence"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the original name Charles Schultz had for Peanuts?", "answer":0, "answers":["Li'l Folks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the original name Charles Schultz had for Peanuts", "answer":0, "answers":["Li'l folk s"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the original name of \"Little Rascals\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Our Gang"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the original name of Paul McCartney's fictional church cleaner 'Eleanor Rigby'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Miss Daisy Hawkins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the Oscar-winning theme song from \"Breakfast at Tiffany's\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Moon River"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the relationship between Superman and Supergirl?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cousin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the relationship between Superman and Supergirl", "answer":0, "answers":["Cousin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the setting for \"The Sound of Music\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Austria"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was the working title for The Beatles' song, 'Yesterday'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrambled Eggs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What was used for blood in the film 'psycho'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chocolate syrup"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What were Wilma Flintstone and Betty Rubble's maiden names?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slaghoople and Mcbricker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What's the name of B.B. King's guitar?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lucille"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"What's the name of the Mummy in the film \"The Mummy\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Imhotep"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Whats the smallest size grand piano?", "answer":0, "answers":["A Baby Grand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When danger appeared, Quick Draw McGraw became which super hero?", "answer":0, "answers":["El KaBong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When danger appeared, Quick Draw McGraw became which super hero", "answer":0, "answers":["El kabong"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When not a Birdman, what does Ray Randall do for a living?", "answer":0, "answers":["Police officer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When not a Birdman, what does Ray Randall do for a living", "answer":0, "answers":["Police officer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When not fighting crime, what did Underdog do for a living?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shoeshine boy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When not fighting crime, what did Underdog do for a living", "answer":0, "answers":["Shoeshine boy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When Tweety exclaimed, \"I thought I saw a putty tat!\", who did he see?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Sylvester"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"When Tweety exclaimed, \"I thought I saw a putty tat!\", who did he see\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Sylvester"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where are Rocket J. Squirel and Bullwinkle Moose from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frostbite Falls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where are Rocket J. Squirel and Bullwinkle Moose from", "answer":0, "answers":["Frostbite falls"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did Clark Kent attend college?", "answer":0, "answers":["Metropolis University"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did Clark Kent attend college", "answer":0, "answers":["Metropolis university"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did George Harrison discover gold?", "answer":0, "answers":["Witwatersrand"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did George of the Jungle live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Imgwee Gwee Valley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did George of the Jungle live", "answer":0, "answers":["Imgwee gwee valley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did Mighty Mouse get his superpowers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Supermarket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where did Mighty Mouse get his superpowers", "answer":0, "answers":["The supermarket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where do Rocky and Bullwinkle play football?", "answer":0, "answers":["What'samatta University"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where do Rocky and Bullwinkle play football", "answer":0, "answers":["What'samatta u niversity"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where does George Jetson work?", "answer":0, "answers":["Spacely Sprockets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where does George Jetson work", "answer":0, "answers":["Spacely sprockets"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where does Gonzo from the Muppet Show come from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Outer space"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where does Yogi Bear Live?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jellystone Park"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where does Yogi Bear Live", "answer":0, "answers":["Jellystone park"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where does young Anakin Skywalker come from?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tatooine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Where is the Rock and Roll Hall Of Fame?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cleveland, Ohio"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which 1960's group sang a song inspired by 'Alice In Wonderland'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Jefferson Airplane"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which 1980's Pink Floyd album was made into a film that starred Bob Geldof, and featured the artwork of cartoonist Gerald Scarfe?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Wall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which actor played the role of Chewbacca in the Star Wars trilogy?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Mayhew"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which actor said, \"Love means never having to say you're sorry\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ryan O'Neil"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which actor won Oscars twice for 'best male performance' in the '90s?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Hanks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which actress won the 2002 Academy Award for best actress in a leading role, for her part in the movie, 'Monster's Ball'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Halle Berry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which Australian duo took 13 nominations and 10 wins at the ARIA awards?", "answer":0, "answers":["Savage Garden"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which band does Eddie Vedder with?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pearl Jam"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which band included rock greats Roy Orbison, Tom Petty, George Harrison, and Bob Dylan?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Travelling Wilburys"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which basketball star played a genie in 'Kazaam'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shaquille O'Neal"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which beatle was the first to release a solo record?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ringo Starr"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which Beatle wrote The Octopus's song?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ringo Starr"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which brand of guitar is played by Jimmy Page, Slash, and Brian May?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gibson Les Paul"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which British group holds the record for the album to remain in the US Billboard charts for the longest time?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pink Floyd"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which british group recorded the 1983 hit 'Owner Of A Lonely Heart'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Yes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which character in \"Forrest Gump\" loved shrimp?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Bubba"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which character sang \"Come Out, Come Out, Wherever You Are\" in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Glinda"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which character sang, \"When you wish upon a star..\" in Disney's \"Pinocchio\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jiminy Cricket"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which comedy duo did the famous, \"Who's on first?\" routine?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Abbott and Costello"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which comic is drawn by Sam Keith?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Maxx"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which comic strip was banned from \"Stars and Stripes\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Beetle Bailey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which comic strip was banned from \"Stars and Stripes\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Beetle bailey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which country and western singer is known as the 'okie from muskogee'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Merle Haggard"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which Elton John song was re-recorded as a requiem for Lady Diana Spencer?", "answer":0, "answers":["Candle In The Wind"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which famous male actor made his name in 'I Dream Of Jeannie'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Larry Hagman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which film preceded 'Magnum Force' and 'The Enforcer'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dirty Harry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which films are about the Corleone family?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Godfather films"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which formber Beatle released the hit single \"My Sweet Lord\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Harrison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which German duo have sold over 85 million records?", "answer":0, "answers":["Modern Talking"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which instruments is used to tune the orchestra?", "answer":0, "answers":["Oboe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which large tuned orchestral drum is also known as a kettledrum?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tympani"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which magician did Lothar assist?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mandrake"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which movie is the highest grossing movie of all time?", "answer":0, "answers":["Titanic"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which native of Flint, Michigan, once advised us to \"drive your Chevrolet through the USA\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pat Boone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which of Beethoven's symphonies was the legendary \"Incomplete\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["The 9th Symphony"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which of Paul Simon's musical characters was told to hop on the bus?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which planet was the \"Planet of the Apes\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Earth"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which singer is a former school teacher?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sheryl Crow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which singer/songwriter worked in a factory making toilets for airplanes before he recorded 'Aint No Sunshine'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bill Withers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which superhero loves peace enough to kill for it?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peacemaker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which superhero loves peace enough to kill for it", "answer":0, "answers":["Peacemaker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which TV horse could talk?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mr. Ed"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Which was the first 'Indiana Jones' film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Raiders Of The Lost Ark"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"White Room' was a hit off which Eric Clapton album?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cream"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who 'imagined' a better world?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Lennon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who advised us to 'break on through to the other side'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Morrison (of The Doors)"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who always tried to kill Krazy Kat?", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain Marvel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who always tried to kill Krazy Kat", "answer":0, "answers":["Captain marvel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who appeared in 'St. Elmo's Fire', 'The Scarlett Letter' and 'Striptease'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Demi Moore"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who appeared solo at the Woodstock festival after leaving 'The Lovin' Spoonful'?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Sebastian"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who are the lead singers of the band \"Full Metal Racquets\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Mcenroe and Pat Cash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who began his career with 'The Yardbirds' and established himself as one of the best rock guitarists of his generation?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eric Clapton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who began his professional career with Black Sabbath?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ozzy Osbourne"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who co-starred with Julie Andrews in \"Mary Poppins\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dick Van Dyke"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who collaborated with John Lennon on 'Whatever Gets You Through The Night'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elton John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did a version of 'One Bourbon, One Scotch, One Beer' on his 1977 debut album?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Thorogood"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did Charlie Becker play in 'The Wizard of Oz'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The mayor of the munchkins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did Larry Hagman portray in the TV series 'Dallas'?", "answer":0, "answers":["J.R. Ewing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did Pat Sajak play on the soapie 'Days Of Our Lives'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kevin Hathaway"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did Patrick Duffy portray in the TV series 'Dallas'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bobby Ewing"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did the music for the 1970's film 'Saturday Night Fever'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bee Gees"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did the voices of Bugs Bunny, Sylvester and Tweety Pie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mel Blanc"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who did Vivian Vance play on 'The Lucy Show'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vivian Bagley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed '2001: A Space Odyssey' and 'A Clockwork Orange'.", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley Kubrick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed 'The Shining'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stanley Kubrick"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed \"Jurassic Park III?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Joe Johnston"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed citizen kane?", "answer":0, "answers":["Orson Welles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed the classic thriller 'The Birds'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alfred Hitchcock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed the film 'Ordinary People'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Redford"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed the film 'The Birds' from Daphne du Maurier?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alfred Hitchcock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed the Movie 'Psycho' from Robert Bloch?", "answer":0, "answers":["Alfred Hitchcock"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who directed the movie \"Blade Runner\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ridley Scott"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who discovered gold on the Witwatersrand?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Harrison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who does the voice for Yoda in the Star Wars films?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank Oz"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who drew the comic 'The Maxx'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sam Keith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who founded 'Live Aid' and 'Band Aid'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Geldof & Midge Ure"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who had, next to Samuel Jackson, a leading roll in 'Unbreakable'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bruce Willis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who hosted the 1997 Grammy Awards?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ellen Degeneres"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who invented James Bond ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ian Fleming"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who invented the electrical bass?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leo Fender"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who invented the synthesiser ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Moog"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Declan Patrick McManus better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Costello"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Donald Duck's uncle?", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrooge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Donald Duck's uncle", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrooge"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Gordon Sumner better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sting"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is James Bonds Recurring Foe?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ernst Stavro Blofeld"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is lead guitarist for Guns'n'Roses?", "answer":0, "answers":["Slash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is married to Eddie Van Halen?", "answer":0, "answers":["Valerie Bertanelli"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is married to Valerie Bertanelli?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eddie Van Halen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Melanie Griffith's mother?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tippi Hedren"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Reginald Dwight known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elton John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Robert van Winkle?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vanilla Ice"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Sally Brown's sweet baboo?", "answer":0, "answers":["Linus"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Sally Brown's sweet baboo", "answer":0, "answers":["Linus van pelt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Scooby Doo's nephew??", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrappy Doo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Scooby Doo's son", "answer":0, "answers":["Scrappy doo"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Snoopy's arch enemy?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Red Baron"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Snoopy's arch enemy", "answer":0, "answers":["The Red Baron"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is stationed at Camp Swampy in the comic strips?", "answer":0, "answers":["Beetle Bailey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is stationed at Camp Swampy in the comic strips", "answer":0, "answers":["Beetle bailey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Steveland Morris better known as?", "answer":0, "answers":["Stevie Wonder"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the autor of the song 'Blue Suede Shoes'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carl Perkins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the elder statesman of 'british blues', and fronted 'The Bluesbreakers'?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Mayall"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the fastest mouse in all of Mexico?", "answer":0, "answers":["Speedy Gonzalez"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the lead singer of 'The Doors'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Morrison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the lead singer of limp bizkit?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred Durst"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the lead singer of the Rolling Stones?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mick Jagger"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the lead vocalist of U2?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bono"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the main character in 'Touched By An Angel'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Monica"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the male lead in the \"Naked Gun\" movies?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Leslie Nielsen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the only singer to have no.1 hits in the 50's, 60's, 70's, 80's and 90's?", "answer":0, "answers":["Cliff Richard"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is the voice of Darth Vadar?", "answer":0, "answers":["James Earl Jones"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Tippi Hedren's daughter?", "answer":0, "answers":["Melanie Griffith"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who is Warren Beatty's sister?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shirley MacLaine"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who killed Kenny?", "answer":0, "answers":["They"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who married Mutt Lange?", "answer":0, "answers":["Shania Twain"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who married Shania Twain?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert \"Mutt\" Lange\""], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who patrols Gotham City?", "answer":0, "answers":["Batman and Robin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who play Captian Jean-Luc Picard in Star Trek the Next Generation?", "answer":0, "answers":["Patrick Stewart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played 'Johnny Mnemonic'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Keanu Reeves"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played 'The Scorpion King' in the recent movie 'The Mummy Returns'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dwight Johnson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played \"Robin\" to Val Kilmer's \"Batman\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christopher O'Donnell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Bobby Ewing in the TV series 'Dallas'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Patrick Duffy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Brad Pitt's cop partner in the movie \"Seven\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Morgan Freeman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Charlie in Charlies Angels?", "answer":0, "answers":["John Forsythe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Clyde to Faye Dunaway's Bonnie?", "answer":0, "answers":["Warren Beatty"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played commander Riker in 'Star Trek'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jonathan Frakes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Dorothy in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Judy Garland"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Dr. Frankenfurter in the pop-culture film 'The Rocky Horror Picture Show?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tim Curry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Dr. Kildare?", "answer":0, "answers":["Richard Chamberlain"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Eddie in the pop-culture film 'The Rocky Horror Picture Show?", "answer":0, "answers":["Meat Loaf"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Garth in \"Wayne's World\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dana Carvey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played George Costanza on 'Seinfeld'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jason Alexander"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Hopalong Cassidy?", "answer":0, "answers":["William Boyd"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played in the film 'Ragtime' after 20 years offscreen?", "answer":0, "answers":["James Cagney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Kevin Hathaway on the soapie 'Days Of Our Lives'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pat Sajak"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Louis in 'Interview With The Vampire'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brad Pitt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Matt Helm in the movies?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dean Martin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Queen Amidala in the latest 'Star Wars' film?", "answer":0, "answers":["Natalie Portman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Scarlette O'Hara in \"Gone With the Wind\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vivien Leigh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played Steve Erkel in 'Family Matters'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jaleel White"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the 'Universal Soldier'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jean-Claude Van Damme"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the 'Wicked Witch of the West' in \"The Wizard of Oz\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Margaret Hamilton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the Agent james Bond in the 1966 film 'Casino Royale'?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Niven"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the first James Bond?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sean Connery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"Braveheart\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mel Gibson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"Castaway\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Hanks"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"Erin Brokovich\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Julia Roberts"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"Mission Impossible\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tom Cruise"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"Snatch\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Brad Pitt"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"The Mask\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jim Carrey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the lead in the movie \"The Matrix\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Keanu Reeves"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the mayor of the munchkins in 'The Wizard of Oz'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlie Becker"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the murder victim in the original version of 'Psycho'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Janet Leigh"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the president of the U.S in 'Air Force One'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harrison Ford"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the role of Richard Blaine in Casablanca?", "answer":0, "answers":["Humphrey Bogart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the title role in the 'Mad Max' series of films?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mel Gibson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who played the title role in the 1978 version of 'Superman'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christopher Reeve"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who plays many voices, such as Dr Nick, and Moe on 'The Simpsons'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Hank Azaria"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who plays the character of the only escapee from Alcatraz in the movie \"The Rock\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sean Connery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who plays the lead role in The Usual Suspects?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kevin Spacey"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who portrayed Han Solo in \"Star Wars\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Harrison Ford"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who portrayed Moses in \"The Ten Commandments\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Charlton Heston"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who produced 'Sgt Pepper's Lonely Hearts Club Band'?", "answer":0, "answers":["George Martin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who produced, directed and starred in \"Citizen Kane\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Orson Welles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who recorded 'A Boy Named Sue'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Johnny Cash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who recorded the 1957 hit \"Tammy\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Debby Reynolds"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who recorded the 1969 hit \"Space Oddity\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["David Bowie"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who recorded the lengthy song: \"In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida\" in 1969?\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Iron Butterfly"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who released 'Time, Love and Tenderness' in 1981?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Bolton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who released 'Tuesday Night Music Club' in 1993?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sheryl Crow"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who released a chart-busting album in 1976 which featured 'The Lido Shuffle'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Boz Scaggs"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who released the double album 'Goodbye Yellow Brick Road' in 1973?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elton John"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who runs Andy Capp's favorite pub?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jack and Jill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who said 'you'd be surprised how much it costs to look this cheap'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dolly Parton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'All Right Now'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Free"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Any Way You Want Me'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Presley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Bad Case Of Loving You'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Robert Palmer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Beat It'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Michael Jackson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Beauty and the Beast'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Celine Dion"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Born In The USA'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bruce Springsteen"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Forever and Ever, Amen'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Randy Travis"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Good Morning To You?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mildred and Patty Hill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'I'm A Believer'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Monkees"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'In The Air Tonight'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Phil Collins"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Islands In The Stream' with Dolly Parton?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kenny Rogers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Islands In The Stream' with Kenny Rogers?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dolly Parton"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Jet Airliner'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Miller Band"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Mull of Kintyre'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Wings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'Rescue Me'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fontella Bass"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'That's Alright Mama'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Elvis Presley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'We've only just begun'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Carpenters"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang 'You Can Call Me Al'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Simon"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang about 'Commitment'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Leann Rhimes"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang about 'The Boogie Woogie Bugle Boy Of Company B'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Andrews Sisters"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang about Desmond and Molly Jones?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Beatles"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang for 'Bad company' and 'Free', then went out on his own?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul Rodgers"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang Puff The Magic Dragon?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter, Paul and Mary"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang the song \"Pretty Woman?\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Roy Orbison"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sang with 'The Dakotas'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Billy J. Kramer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who says, \"Th_th_th_that's all folks!\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Porky pig"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who says, \"Th-th-th-that's all folks!\"\"", "answer":0, "answers":["Porky Pig"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who shot Bruce Wayne's parents?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who shot Bruce Wayne's parents", "answer":0, "answers":["Chill"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sings 'Sweet Home Alabama'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lynyrd Skynyrd"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sings \"Imitation Of Life\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["R.E.M."], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who sings and plays the theme song for the TV show 'Frasier'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kelsey Grammer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who starred as 'ouboet' in the first TV series of 'Orkney Snork Nie'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Frank Opperman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who starred in 'Conan The Barbarian'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Arnold Schwarzenegger"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who starred in the 1952 film 'Niagara'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Marilyn Monroe"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who starred in the film 'The Man With Two Brains'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Steve Martin"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who starred in the film version of 'To Kill A Mockingbird'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gregory Peck"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who starred with John Travolta in the movie \"Broken Arrow\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Christian Slater"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who took dictation from Perry Mason?", "answer":0, "answers":["Della Street"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wanted 'a lover with a slow hand'?", "answer":0, "answers":["The Pointer Sisters"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wanted 'a new drug'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Huey Lewis and The News"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was 'hooked on a feeling'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Blue Suede"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was a member of 'Crosby, Stills and Nash' and 'The Hollies'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Graham Nash"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was always trying to get rent from Andy Capp?", "answer":0, "answers":["Percy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was always trying to get rent from Andy Capp", "answer":0, "answers":["Percy"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Barney Rubble's best friend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred Flintstone"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was born on Krypton?", "answer":0, "answers":["Superman"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was C3PO's sidekick in \"Star Wars\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["R2D2"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Carl in Five Easy Pieces before going to Walton's Mountain?", "answer":0, "answers":["Waite"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Chief Marshall of the Mickey Mouse Club?", "answer":0, "answers":["Walt Disney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Daisy the dog's owners", "answer":0, "answers":["Blond"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Dick Dastardley's pet", "answer":0, "answers":["Muttley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Dick Dastardly's pet?", "answer":0, "answers":["Muttley"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Dr. Zhivago's great love?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lara"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Fred Flinstone's best friend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Barney Rubble"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was John Wayne's musical co-star in true grit?", "answer":0, "answers":["Glen Campbell"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Lauren Bacall's first husband?", "answer":0, "answers":["Humphrey Bogart"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was Miss Hungary in 1936?", "answer":0, "answers":["Zsa-Zsa Gabor"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the alter ego of 'The Incredible Hulk'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Dr. David Banner"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the black assistant of Mandrake the Magician?", "answer":0, "answers":["Lothar"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the Cisco Kid's faithful sidekick?", "answer":0, "answers":["Pancho"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the director of 'Terminator' and 'Titanic'?", "answer":0, "answers":["James Cameron"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the first female to enter the Billboard charts in 1985?", "answer":0, "answers":["Whitney Houston"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the first James Bond?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sean Connery"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the first singer in Genesis?", "answer":0, "answers":["Peter Gabriel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the first voice of Mickey Mouse?", "answer":0, "answers":["Walt Disney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the frontman of Nirvana?", "answer":0, "answers":["Kurt Cobain"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the Hulk's first friend?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rick Jones"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the Hulk's first friend", "answer":0, "answers":["Rick jones"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the Indian maiden in Johnny Preston's 'Running Bear'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Little White Dove"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the oldest member of The Beatles?", "answer":0, "answers":["Ringo Starr"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the only songwriter to win the Eurovision Song Contest twice?", "answer":0, "answers":["Johnny Logan"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the original voice of Mickey Mouse?", "answer":0, "answers":["Walt Disney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the original voice of Mickey Mouse", "answer":0, "answers":["Walt disney"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the sexy star of Barberella?", "answer":0, "answers":["Jane Fonda"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who was the villain in 'Star Wars'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Darth Vader"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who were Lucy and Ricky's next door neighbours and best friends?", "answer":0, "answers":["Fred and Ethel"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who were the 2 lead characters in the movie Life?", "answer":0, "answers":["Eddie Murphy and Martin Lawrence"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who were the rivals of the T-Birds in the movie \"Grease\"?", "answer":0, "answers":["Scorpions"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote 'Roll Over Beethoven'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Chuck Berry"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote and preformed the soundtrack for Live and let die?", "answer":0, "answers":["Paul McCartney and Wings"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the Nutcracker Suite ?", "answer":0, "answers":["Tchaikovsky"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the opera 'norma'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Vincenzo Bellini"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the opera 'The Giant'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Sergei Prokofiev"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the opera 'The Masked Ball'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Giuseppe Verdi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the opera 'Tosca'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Giacomo Puccini"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the oprea 'La Traviata'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Guiseppe Verdi"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the song 'Do They Know It's Christmas' with Bob Geldof?", "answer":0, "answers":["Midge Ure"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote the song 'Do They Know It's Christmas' with Midge Ure?", "answer":0, "answers":["Bob Geldof"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who wrote Tubular Bells?", "answer":0, "answers":["Mike Oldfield"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Who's first release was 'Talking Heads 77'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Psycho Killer"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Whose films include 'Giant', 'Written On The Wind' and 'A Farewell To Arms'?", "answer":0, "answers":["Rock Hudson"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Whose theme song was Back In The Saddle Again?", "answer":0, "answers":["Gene Autry's"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"With which period in music do we associate composers such as Beethoven, Mozart and Haydn?", "answer":0, "answers":["Classical period"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"With which period in music do we associate composers such as Tchaikovsky, Mendelssohn, and Chopin?", "answer":0, "answers":["Romantic period"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"With which period in music do we associate with composers such as Bach, Handel and Vivaldi?", "answer":0, "answers":["Baroque Period"], "source":""},
  {"category_id":"ENTERTAINMENT", "lang":"en", "tags":["ENTERTAINMENT"], "question":"Younger version of Aquaman", "answer":0, "answers":["Aqualad"], "source":""}
]
